Joseph Oluwadara

BLOCKCHAIN SECURITY RESEARCHER

jsatimehin@gmail.com
Github
LinkedIn
Twitter
Website

PROFILE

I am a Smart Contract Security Researcher, experienced in writing and auditing solidity smart contracts. With a deep level understanding of the EVM opcodes, Solidity, Assembly and Blockchains, I have audited both simple and complex codebases totalling over 100,000 SLOC in public audit contests alone.

Some of my tools include:

- 1. Hardhat and Remix for smart contract writing, testing,
- 2. Echidna and Foundry for fuzz testing and fork testing against live blockchain instances.
- 2. Automated tools like Slither for static testing.

I have experience auditing and writing different smart contracts including: AMMs, Fungible and Non Fungible tokens, Sales contracts, Auction contracts, Liquidity staking contracts, Account Abstraction Wallets, Vaults, Factories, Proxies and Upgradeable contracts.

I currently do smart contract audits at Code4rena, Sherlock and ImmuneFi. I also participate in different CTFs and I have completed a few such as Ethernaut from Openzeppelin, Damn Vulnerable Defi, Secureum Bootcamp and more.

Some of my skills include:

- Solidity
- Assembly: YUL
- Foundry
- Hardhat
- JavaScript
- NodeJS
- Rust
- NextJS & React

EXPERIENCE

Smart Contract Security Researcher

April 2023 - Present

- Participated in 17 Audits Contests in Code4rena finding 28 H/M.
- Participated in 5 Audits Contests in Sherlock finding 9 H/M.
- Found Bugs in two projects listed on ImmuneFi, [Cannot Be Disclosed].
- Completed one Private Audit.

All these are confirmed bugs with payouts from the protocol teams. More info $\underline{\mathsf{here}}$

Blockchain Developer (Contract)

Astra Metaverse

September 2022 - January 2023

- Created an ERC 1155 token smart contract and minter
- Created a Metaverse Marketplace smart contract
- Writing APIs to connect with the smart contracts on the blockchain

Blockchain Developer

COLLECT WAVES

May 2022 - December 2022

- Created & Tested an Music NFT smart Contract
- Designed an NFT market place smart contract and NFT minter
- Writing APIs to connect with the smart contracts on the blockchain
- Creation of Tokens.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, MATHEMATICS
Federal University of Abeokuta, Ogun, Nigeria.
2018 - 2022